mahak-charity.org 2006-06-18

# Privacy Policy

**  
** ****Privacy Policy ** ****  
**(Publication date: May 2003)** **

****MAHAK maintains this website in order to provide you with information about our work, and to enable you to interact with us, web base and also paper base. This policy describes MAHAK's activities ** ** ****through our website.  
** YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS POLICY. **

**MAHAK website has several features. In addition to providing descriptions of our programs and how we help children in need in our local country, Iran, the website provides you with the opportunity to take action to help improve the lives of children stricken with cancer and help them to survive, including the option to read latest news of MAHAK activities and reports.  
We encourage you to read the entire policy as it sets forth our understanding with you when you visit our website.  
Throughout this policy, you will see the terms "MAHAK," "we," "our," and "us" - these terms refer to MAHAK Society. You will also see the terms “I,” "you," "your," and "yours" - these terms refer to visitors to and users of our Website.**

**_A. Do I have to submit any personal information in order to visit the MAHAK website? _  
We do not ask you to submit personal information (information that allows us to identify you) if you are just browsing at our website. If you choose to take advantage of some of our services, we will sometimes request personal information. For example, if you ask to sponsor a child, or be a volunteer member, we will ask you to provide us with personal information including your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address and other identifying information. **

**_B. What are "cookies," and does the MAHAK website use "cookies" or “pixels”?_** **  
A "cookie" is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from MAHAK's web server and is stored on your computer's hard drive. MAHAK do not use/uses cookies.  
In addition, MAHAK do not use/uses pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partner, DoubleClick. These files enable DoubleClick to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by DoubleClick, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies and the pixel technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, postal address, telephone number, or e-mail address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy.> **

**_C. Does MAHAK ever collect personal information, such as my name, postal address or credit card information, through its website? _  
At certain sections on our website, you may be asked to submit personal information. This includes, but may not be limited to, your name, postal address, zip code, telephone number, organization name and e-mail address. In addition, in order to make an on-line contribution to MAHAK, or to submit a membership form, we may ask you to provide credit card or other billing information. **

**_D. How is personal information used by MAHAK? _  
Personal information will be used internally by MAHAK to provide you with information about MAHAK's work and ways that you can further support our efforts. **

**You do not have to disclose any personal information if you do not want to. You can always decide not to use those website services or features that require such information. Our goal is to offer you convenient online services that match your interests.**

**_E. Does MAHAK share personal information with third parties? _  
MAHAK may not share any personal information with third parties. The information that you give in order to fill the forms will come to MAHAK office to pass official process.  **

****PLEASE BE AWARE: ******use of multiple e-mail addresses, postal addresses and/or name spellings will impact our ability to administer your file. Please be sure that we have accurate information from you. **

****EXCEPTIONS TO OPTING OUT: ** MAHAK reserves the right to share your personal information in certain situations: **

****1\. Credit Card Transactions. ** MAHAK hires third parties to provide credit card processing services and order fulfillment services. If you have opted to donate on-line, or become a sponsor, we may share your personal information, including credit card or billing information, with these service providers. We make an effort to require all third party service-providers to hold personal information in strict confidence. While we believe these other companies are upstanding and will treat your personal information responsibly, we do not own or control them. **

****2\. Necessity. ** If the law or a regulatory authority compels us, MAHAK will disclose personal information. Also, if we have reason to believe that there has been some inappropriate interference with or use of MAHAK website or services, or if we have reason to believe that one of our website users may have been injured or has harmed some other party, we will disclose personal information as we deem appropriate or if asked by a legal or regulatory authority. **

****_G. Does MAHAK share non-personal (aggregated) information with third parties?_ **  
Yes, MAHAK may share aggregate, statistical and other non-personal information with our advertisers and other third parties. For example, we may share the number of our website visitors from various states with an advertiser, or the number of visitors to our website. These aggregate statistics do not include personal information. **

****_H. What rules apply if I "click" over to another website?_ **  
In order to provide certain services and materials, MAHAK contracts with other companies and individuals to support our website activities. These additional services and materials may include providing "links" to other websites from our website. Except as may be outlined in this policy, the privacy policies of MAHAK do not apply to any third-party sites. Anytime you leave MAHAK website, we have no control regarding what information may be collected about you, nor do we control what third parties might do with the information. It is important that you review any privacy policies on third-party sites carefully, BEFORE you use any services or programs offered. **

**_I. How does MAHAK website provide security and confidentiality of my personal information? _  
MAHAK has built in several layers of security into our system. All on-line transactions are done on a secure server. This information remains confidential and is not shared with any outside sources. **

**_J. Does MAHAK ever change its website policies? _  
From time to time, MAHAK may add features or services to our website. This may include collecting different types of information and/or changing the uses of the information. In these instances, we will endeavor to edit this policy in a timely fashion to explain the new practices. PLEASE check these policies occasionally to find out if there are any changes (there is a date of publication at the top). If we make substantial changes in our web-site policies, we will try to include an announcement on our home page and elsewhere so that you will know to look for the revised policy. **

**_K. Who do I contact with questions or comments about the privacy policy? _  
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please [Contact Us](mailto:info@mahak-charity.org%20%3cinfo@mahak-charity.org%3e). In the alternative, you may contact us by: **

****Regular Mail: **  
MAHAK International Relations  
Attention: Internet Dept.  
P.O. Box: 19395-5445 **

**Remember, you are under no obligation to disclose any personal information if you do not want to. If you are not comfortable MAHAK's uses of information, you may always decide to opt out or decide not to use those website services or features that require personal information. If you wish to change how MAHAK uses your personal information,[ ](https://www.savethechildren.org/homesignin.jsp) please  _[Contact](mailto:info@mahak-charity.org%20%3cinfo@mahak-charity.org%3e) _ ** **  **
